[FRENCI] These remnants
are all we managed to salvage.
We discovered them
in the guild fireplace.
Everything else
had already turned to ash.
[Kivia exhales softly]
[KIVIA] What's this?
Most likely a contract receipt.
[Kivia breathes shakily]
His name is Mahaeyzel Zelkoff.
[KIVIA] It's imperative that
we get him into custody.
[FRENCI] I doubt
that will be possible.
I imagine he's already
left this town behind.
One way or another.
[RAJIT] Permission denied.
I don't have the authorization.
I'm aware your hands are bound
by the ropes of bureaucracy.
But, look, our circumstances
have changed.
I come bearing a special order
for his immediate release.
[Rajit sighs]
I'm to believe this is genuine?
[VENETIM] There can be no doubt.
It has the glorious seal
of Galtuile.
The local military supervisor
was very accommodating.
Oh, naturally, you're free
to confirm its veracity.
Though locking up a hero
hardly seems a punishment
to begin with.
It's more like a holiday.
He's sleeping blissfully,
resting in safety and security
while we others risk it all.
Am I wrong?
[Rajit sighs]
Wait here a minute.
I'll go confirm.
By all means, do!
[♪ opening theme song playing]
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[TEORITTA] My knight,
your divine muse
desires an outing.
Does your heart
not ache to explore?
Your love of zeff butter
is becoming an obsession.
I shall not suffer
further confinement here.
I wish to go outside! [grunts]
Well, that's not
our call to make.
[NORGALLE]
If the goddess wants an outing,
I can think
of nothing more fitting
than a trip to the
Dujin Art Museum.
It boasts a collection
of masterpieces
from the middle classical era,
while the building itself
showcases
modern Nashida
architectural techniques.
Truly a visual triumph!
Naturally,
as a strategic port...
What's there to like about
a dusty old museum?
Nothing can beat the ocean.
The view's great
as you fly out to sea.
And aerial hunting in the forest
is always fun.
[XYLO] Not everyone can fly,
you know.
At least suggest something
that someone who isn't a dragon
would enjoy.
What, you don't care
if dragons are happy?
My knight,
any activity would suffice.
I simply wish
to go into town today!
Out of the question.
Or have you forgotten
that you have
a target on your back?
I doubt that they'll ever
let us out again.
[Teoritta groans]
How very disheartening.
[KIVIA] It's fine.
I can grant you permission.
[TEORITTA] Is that so?
But you can't go any further
than the Temple.
It's close to the barracks.
I'll arrange a full security
detail for you.
Kivia, on occasion, you are
the herald of good tidings!
To what do we owe all these?
Yeah? Well, I'm guessing
there's some reason.
There isn't.
I'm simply hoping to brighten
goddess Teoritta's day
in whatever way I can.
[TEORITTA] How admirable!
Xylo, you should seek
to curry my favor as well.
[XYLO] You can't just
demand that.
It's settled.
Inform High Priest Marlen
of the plan.
I'll send a unit
of my most trustworthy soldiers.
[XYLO] You won't be joining us?
[KIVIA] Not today.
-[Teoritta exclaiming, grunting]
-[KIVIA] I'm busy.
Understood.
And I will be sure to keep
a close eye on Teoritta.
[indistinct chatter]
♪
[GIRL 1] It's really her!
[BOY 1] The Great Goddess
of Swords, Teoritta!
Goddess, can you sign my tunic?
I'd love for you
to sign my book, too!
[TEORITTA]
Your prayers are answered!
Ample blessings shall now be
bestowed upon you
by the grace
of the great goddess Teoritta!
-[GIRL 1] Hooray!
-[BOY 2] Do mine next!
[GIRL 2] I want
your blessing too, Goddess!
According to superstition,
a goddess' signature
wards off bad luck.
I guess some people
still believe in that.
Well, it seems harmless.
[Teoritta hums]
-[WOMAN] Blessed goddess.
-Oh?
Here, we brought you
some nice treats.
You're the same size
as my sweet little grandchild,
and yet you go around fighting
Demon Blights on our behalf.
[TEORITTA]
Ah, there is nothing to it!
Not for a truly mighty goddess!
Are you watching this,
my knight?
Such is the appropriate
treatment of a goddess,
which you should
pridefully seek to mimic.
But, first, you may
partake of my treats!
You're too generous.
Though, I should check
for poison.
I'm sorry, ma'am...
Isn't that the
Demon Lord hunter...
...but I'll have to
confiscate these.
The Thunder Falcon!
His name's Xylo Forbartz,
and I really
-want his autograph!
-What?
All these people
know about me, too?
-[MARLEN] They do.
-Uh?
[MARLEN] You're quite popular
these days.
High Priest Marlen.
Rumors have a way of spreading.
They know about your deeds
at Mureed Fortress
and Sodrick's Shell.
[laughs] But I'm just
a lowly penal hero.
[overlapping chatter]
[MARLEN] I doubt these children
can yet grasp what that means.
As for myself,
I've had cause to reevaluate.
My niece has told me
a great deal about you.
Patausche may be too noble
for her own good.
She values honor
above even her own well-being.
A desire to be remembered
for great deeds, I suppose.
Rather troubling,
don't you agree?
Perhaps.
There are more like her
than you'd think.
Especially fighting the battle
against the Demon Blight.
Though, I'm sure it's harder
when it's your own niece.
True.
I have always cared
for Patausche
as though she were
my own daughter.
If anyone were to betray her
or cause her undue sorrow,
I would intervene.
[XYLO] Uh...
Listen, Xylo Forbartz,
I have heard
that you have a fiancée...
-[bell tolling]
-[both gasp]
-[MAN 1] The bell!
-[MAN 2] That could only mean...
-[Xylo grunts]
-Xylo, what does it portend?
-[MARLEN] An attack.
-[Teoritta gasps]
When those bells
are rung in Ioff City,
it means we are under siege.
[bell tolling in distance]
[KIVIA] Uh?
[VENETIM] Uh?
Greetings! I wasn't expecting
company.
Enough.
What are you doing in here?
[VENETIM] Me?
I realized I had made a mistake
in a recent report,
so I figured I should
try to correct it.
Are you aware
that crucial military
and Temple documents
are stored in this room?
Only officers
are permitted to enter.
Oh, I had no idea!
I must humbly
beg your forgiveness.
Prepare for combat,
and stay out of this place.
But of course!
I'll go assemble
the Hero Unit at once.
I do hope
we can keep this
little incident between us.
[steps receding]
[door opens, closes]
[grunts softly]
[VENETIM] I wish you'd
consider the fact
that I have to
free you every time
you get yourself locked up.
Oh? I didn't know
you were back.
Well, hello there, Xylo.
I'm glad to see you're thriving.
I hear you've been
having quite a time
while I was locked away.
My heart broke for you
from within my prison cell.
Yet somehow you're just
as smug as you always are.
And who do we have here?
The famous goddess, correct?
[Teoritta grunts softly]
[RHYNO] It is truly
an honor to meet you.
The name is Rhyno.
I proudly serve as the artillery
for Penal Hero Unit 9004.
In fact, you could say that
Comrade Xylo and I are partners.
[Xylo grunts softly]
We're nothing of the sort.
Hey, Venetim,
I'm starting to think
we busted him out
way too early.
Just looking at the bastard
-pisses me off.
-[gasps]
You're the one who insisted
I get him released!
[XYLO] A volunteer hero
who keeps getting
thrown in a cell?
What the hell
were you thinking?
I wanted to help,
to be of service
to the poor, vulnerable souls
getting trampled by faeries,
which is why I had no choice
but to do what I did.
[XYLO] "Had no choice"
but to shell civilian houses
into oblivion?
-That makes no damn sense.
-[RHYNO] Agree to disagree.
For now, might I suggest
we join forces
and fight our way through this
latest round of trouble.
Anyway...
Ioff Cheg is the Port district.
It seems that's where
the faeries first originated.
The horde then moved on
to this location.
That's where they occupied
Tui Jia, the Coral Tower.
[grunts] A key part
of our coastal defense.
[explosion]
[VENETIM] The horde
has a Demon Lord with it,
which could taint Tui Jia
until it transforms
into a faerie.
-It's a trap.
-It's clearly a trap.
-[Xylo grunts]
-[Rhyno chuckles]
[RHYNO] They've got
artillery too, right?
Given the wind direction
and speed,
you could hit anywhere
in Ioff Cheg from there,
meaning they have
the advantage.
[XYLO] They're basically holding
this whole region hostage.
What are Galtuile's orders?
[VENETIM] Ah, well.
Funny you should ask.
The Thirteenth Order
of the Holy Knights
and the Ioff City Guard
will be stationed
in the Inland district,
while the Hero Unit
will act as the sole defense
of the Port district.
[XYLO] Huh?
We're told to hold out
until reinforcements arrive,
at which point,
they'll begin a counterattack.
Got it?
That's their big plan?
To abandon everyone
living in the Port district?
The Noble Alliance
was always going to prioritize
the Inland district!
That's where most of their
government facilities
and noble properties
are located.
[XYLO] Dammit, they only care
about themselves.
Xylo, there's no point
in getting hurt or killed
for a hopeless mission
like this,
-and you know I'm right.
-[XYLO] Meaning?
Perhaps we should strive
to avoid doing anything
overly aggressive.
[TEORITTA] Have you
no concept of shame?
Regardless of the trials
we face, rejoice!
For we have
the immense honor
of being the sole guardians
of the people.
And such battles are well worth
laying down our very lives for!
Stop. I already told you
to get over your bent
for self-sacrifice-
[RHYNO]
What a magnificent goddess!
Your willingness to die
for the cause is inspiring,
and I completely agree.
Comrade Xylo, the time has come
to lend our strength.
Let us join hands and fight
for the hopes and dreams
of these fine people!
Enough already.
It's not as though
we have a choice.
Xylo, I am certain
you shall forge a path.
I have
the utmost faith in you.
[grunts] I'm aware.
Good thing I refuse
to let those assholes
have their way.
They'll regret
underestimating me.
♪
This site shall be
our stronghold!
A sanctuary
for those evacuating.
Let us construct
a sacred seal fence
in accordance
with my blueprints.
[ADVENTURERS] Majesty!
[NORGALLE] Then we harness
the burning embers!
Gather all the food
and sacred seal-infused
cookware you can find.
[ADVENTURERS] On it!
Hold on. What are those
guild people doing here?
Apparently, His Majesty promised
he would give them some work.
Pretty sure he said something
about salaries and titles.
Titles, huh?
The first thing we'll do
is gather some wood!
As much as your arms
can carry!
-[ADVENTURERS] Yes, sir.
-[COMMANDER] Hurry up.
Figures. Though,
I guess it's better
than them becoming highwaymen.
[indistinct chatter]
[gobbling]
[TEORITTA]
It is very hot but very good!
Hey, Tatsuya,
eat up!
You dunce! Not with your hands!
To rush is sheer folly.
So you know, you're spilling
as much as he is.
[footsteps]
[Teoritta grunts]
[RHYNO] Nothing invigorates
the spirit like a hot meal.
Placing top priority
on securing a way to cook...
Norgalle is a born leader.
Quite impressive!
My... his garb is most unusual.
The Neven Artillery
Seal Compound.
That's what it's called,
but I don't know why he's chosen
to wear it to dinner.
I was hoping we'd have
the whole unit back together
at long last.
I take it we will be reuniting
with the rest
of our comrades shortly?
Tsav is currently getting
his arm repaired.
But considering
the circumstances,
they'll likely do
the bare minimum
before deploying him.
[Tsav screams]
And Comrade Jayce?
I'm quite surprised
he isn't already here.
[XYLO] Venetim's working
on it as we speak.
They think sending a dragon
for urban warfare
is too dangerous,
but he'll convince them.
I doubt His Majesty
will leave the base.
And Dotta's more useful
for scouting than fighting.
So it's just the four of us
heading to Tui Jia.
Goes without saying...
That's not gonna be
nearly enough manpower.
[RHYNO] If I may,
I have a suggestion.
[XYLO] Do I even want to know?
[RHYNO] I could always shell
that massive wall down.
The Inland District would
quickly be flooded with faeries,
effectively forcing
the other soldiers
to join the fight.
Thus, solving
our manpower issue.
[Teoritta grunts softly]
[RHYNO] I believe
pain and suffering
should be shared equally
among everyone.
Humans tend
to bond over strife,
so it's beautiful
when you think about it.
Take heed, my knight.
-That man is...
-Yeah, I'm aware.
Denied.
Your moronic plan would
also endanger civilians.
[RHYNO] Hmm?
Do you have a better idea
in mind, Comrade Xylo?
[XYLO] Rhyno,
most people aren't motivated
by the bonds they've formed.
But by profit.
Attack the ships
moored in the harbor.
I assume you can hit them
from here.
[RHYNO] I see, how brilliant.
Well done, Comrade Xylo.
After that, we go there.
We'll take back Tui Jia,
and murder the Demon Lord.
[knocking on door]
[RAJIT] Captain Kivia,
we need your instructions
for the mission.
All right. I'm on my way.
[Kivia sighs]
A foolish order,
no matter how you spin it.
Our hands are tied.
Maintaining the support
of the nobility is paramount,
and there are a lot
of Temple buildings
over in that district as well.
[door opens]
Oops, I'm sorry
for interrupting.
Why are you here?
It was my understanding
that the Hero Unit
was out in the field.
They are.
As their commander,
I would love nothing more
than to be there
rallying their spirits.
But instead,
I must woefully report
that the faeries
have attacked
the sacred seal vessels
in the harbor.
They what?
I imagine the loss
of Temple property
is simply unacceptable.
Which is why, I would like
to ask permission
to deploy our dragon.
You're lying.
Why would the faeries
start by attacking
-sacred seal vessels?
-[door opens]
Captain, a sacred seal vessel
is on fire!
[Rajit sighs]
[SOLDIER] New orders.
The Temple's requesting
our help.
Thank you.
-You're dismissed.
-Right!
[door opens]
I see. You were telling
the truth, then.
[VENETIM] I'm afraid so.
I also found it
difficult to believe
when I first heard the news.
It is a crying shame, isn't it?
[KIVIA] Very well.
Your unit can use its dragon.
Is that wise?
[KIVIA] The Temple's request
is all the reason we need.
We'll also send some soldiers.
Your generosity is
more than appreciated.
Really, thank you.
One last thing,
please give my regards
to High Priest Marlen.
[Kivia grunts]
Go on. What are you saying?
Uh... Oh, I was merely-
You don't even know him!
What are you insinuating?
Hear me out!
I wasn't trying...
Sheer insolence!
High Priest Marlen
is a man of honor!
He's devoted his whole life
to the Temple,
and he's always supported
the Holy Knights!
Yet despite that, you dare-
Please. You have it wrong.
Look, I can explain.
It's simple, really.
I have some advice
about security
-in the underground waterway.
-[Kivia gasps, grunts]
[Rajit gasps]
[exhales sharply]
[all clamoring]
[monsters growling]
[clamoring continues]
[MAN] Get to the shelter!
Xylo, they're coming.
Bogies! From the side, too!
-You're surrounded!
-[XYLO] Got it.
Keep a close eye
on our situation.
Here we go!
[growling]
[RHYNO] Look who's
come out to play.
Bogies are the bane
of artillerymen.
Comrade Xylo, if you don't mind.
-Tatsuya!
-[Tatsuya grunts]
[Tatsuya yelling]
Let's get in there too,
Teoritta.
Yes, I shall now
grant you my blessing!
[XYLO] Time to die!
[RHYNO]
Nothing is more exhilarating
than fighting alongside
a comrade!
-Oh, I'm terribly lucky!
-[Xylo scoffs]
[XYLO] Keep running.
We'll charge our way
-to Tui Jia-
-[DOTTA] Hold on!
There is some kind of
warehouse up ahead.
You should know.
It looks like it has
a Verkle Corp mark on it,
and the braziers are lit.
I think people
are holed up inside.
The faeries are swarming it.
They made a damn shelter?
That timing couldn't be worse!
[RHYNO] What's our next plan
of attack, Comrade Xylo?
My knight, to aid those people
would be most honorable.
Would it not?
I hear you.
-[growling]
-What the...
[monsters growling]
Rhyno, might end up
being a fight to the death.
Prepare yourself.
[RHYNO] I'm always prepared.
To protect the nameless masses,
I would gladly lay down my life.
We're finally having some fun.
[all grunting]
[Rhyno laughs]
[sighs]
[Rhyno exclaims]
The breaking flash seal
was a direct hit.
Oh, we make a great team,
don't you agree?
-Especially you, my goddess.
-[Teoritta gasps]
[RHYNO] Your power
is awe inspiring.
You speak the truth.
Though,
for some strange reason
I find myself feeling ambivalent
about your adulation.
[Rhyno laughs]
[RHYNO] No need
to be uncomfortable.
After all, you and I
are one and the same.
[XYLO]
You two are nothing alike.
The Holy Knights ought to be
on the move by now.
Isn't that right, Venetim?
[VENETIM] Uh, oh, yes!
I also secured authorization
for Jayce to join you,
and got the underground
waterway locked down.
[XYLO] The waterway?
Was it invaded?
Actually, it was
a spur-of-the-moment suggestion.
[XYLO] You went rogue for that?
[RHYNO] Well,
I, for one, approve.
We can't be lax in
defending the urban area.
I sent Frenci
and the other night-gaunts
to defend that sector.
We still don't know
where Spriggan is.
[DOTTA] Um, Xylo?
Up ahead and to the right!
On the roofs!
This is really bad!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
[all mocking]
[RHYNO] They seem
to have lightning staves.
I didn't know they could use
sacred seals.
Seriously? Are those damn
coexisters to blame?
Rhyno!
[RHYNO] My turn.
[Xylo and Teoritta grunting]
[RHYNO] Good. No damage.
Though, it did consume
a fair amount of luminescence.
Dammit all. I would like to duck
into an alley, but these-
[RHYNO] We don't have
the luxury of hesitation.
[XYLO] Wait, no!
[all gasping]
You destroyed all those houses.
[RHYNO] Of course, saving lives
takes top priority.
That had nothing to do with it.
[RHYNO] Now, onward!
To the people
patiently awaiting salvation!
-[SOLDIER 1] Hurry!
-[SOLDIER 2] Kill them all!
[gunfire]
[SOLDIER 3] Don't let them
get to the Inland District!
[SOLDIER 4] Fire!
[monsters screeching]
[SOLDIER 5] Good.
These are the last of them.
Fire!
[gunfire]
I'm surprised they thought
to lock down the waterway.
I wonder
what tipped them off
that we planned to use it
to send in more faeries.
I can't help being impressed
by their foresight.
You knights
have earned my praise.
[soldier 1 gasps]
Who's that? Reveal yourself!
[SOLDIER 2]
It's a faerie! Or a human?
[SOLDIER 3] Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Easy does it.
I would advise you
not to resist.
To suffer a painful death
is truly pitiable.
[knights gasping]
-[slashing]
-[soldiers screaming]
[indistinct chatter]
[KIVIA] Uncle!
Patausche,
I'm grateful that you came.
Faeries have been sighted
in the Inland District.
Indeed. I received word
of it from the guards.
It would appear they entered
through the waterway.
[KIVIA] The military
and the Temple joined forces?
How were you able to coordinate
such a thing, Uncle?
This is no time for us to be
feuding amongst ourselves.
What good is a high priest
if he is unable
to bring everyone together
when it matters the most?
It is a blessing.
This peril will strengthen
the bonds
between Temple and military.
And those very bonds
will ensure
a path to victory
for all humanity.
Well said, Uncle.
Your words are inspiring,
and I will take them to heart.
I will be counting on you,
as ever.
We shall overcome,
if we stick together.
Right.
[MARLEN] Hmm.
May the blessings
of Saint Mahaeyzel
guide and protect us.
[Kivia gasps]
[MARLEN] Now,
let the attack commence.
[Kivia breathes shakily]